Shawn Conway

Poquoson, VA | 747-200-5084 | conwayshawn33@gmail.com Linkedin | Github | Blog

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Full Stack Web Developer with an ongoing desire for learning. With experience in Python and JavaScript and a background in the Hospitality and Medical Cannabis industries, I bring strong skills in organization, attention to detail, and communication. A passion for problem-solving brought me to web development; my focus and teamwork help drive project completion and a productive work environment.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python with Flask, SQL, JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, API, RESTful routing, Fetch requests, SQLite, Formik, Git, Github, Visual Studio Code, Databases

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Conway Property Management - Github | Demo

A website that showcases vacation rentals in the Mid-Atlantic area of the United States.

- Utilized flexbox and custom CSS to design frontend
- Incorporated Formik in sign-up form
- Built frontend with React, Flask backend with API endpoints for Fetch requests, and SQLite for data persistence
- Incorporated berypt to facilitate custom authentication

Video Game Library - Github | Demo

An app that allows users to search and select video games and learn which consoles the game is played on.

- Utilized React and Flask to create a full stack website
- Designed using full CRUD
- Created the database schema
- Developed API backend to handle data persistence and respond to fetch requests

EXPERIENCE

Craft Repair, Hampton, VA

09/2022 - 08/2023

- Machinist
- Developed the skills to use a lathe and other machinery in the facility
- Executed Driveshaft and Rim repair
- Communicated with the welding team to ensure parts were repaired correctly for proper installation
- Calculated precise measurements for cutting and shaping materials

Cannabiotix, Los Angeles, CA

04/2020 - 04/2022

Trimmer

- Delivered 2500 grams of trimmed product in 8 hours on a daily basis; average is usually 300 grams in 8 hours.
- Finished the processing of product before being packaged
- Educated inexperienced trimmers on how to increase productivity

Independent Contractor, Los Angeles, CA

04/2012 - 04/2020

Facility Construction and Production Management

- Contributed to the building of cannabis facilities and production of those facilities
- Managed nurseries and flower rooms
- Oversaw the processing of cannabis plants

Alta Ski Resort, Alta, UT

11/2009 - 04/2012

Chef at Collins' Grill

- Headed the prep and lunch services
- Created menus and catered events for the resort
- Responsible for inventory and ordering of food and food service supplies.
- Decreased food cost by portion control and consistent production

EDUCATION

Flatiron School New York, NY

08/2023 - 12/2023

Full Stack Web Development, Python with Flask and JavaScript program

George Mason University Fairfax, VA

Business, Economics, History